<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Sandbox</title><link>https://markpaulayers.com/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Sandbox</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://markpaulayers.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Now</title><link>https://markpaulayers.com/now/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://markpaulayers.com/now/</guid><description>Ex enim magna excepteur laborum ipsum. Aliquip et incididunt qui laborum fugiat irure voluptate in aute. Laboris eiusmod sint et fugiat magna est nostrud irure. Sit labore irure ut consectetur sunt.
This is a Now page. You should have one too.</description></item><item><title>Alphabet sentences</title><link>https://markpaulayers.com/notes/alphabet-sentences/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://markpaulayers.com/notes/alphabet-sentences/</guid><description>A large fawn jumped quickly over white zinc boxes.
A mad boxer shot a quick, gloved jab to the jaw of his dizzy opponent.
A pox on you, jergens, old beanbag, you’ve squashed my favorite zwieback.
A quick brown fox jumps over the lazy dog.
A quick movement of the enemy will jeopardize six gunboats.
About sixty codfish eggs will make a quarter pound of very fizzy jelly.
Alfredo just must bring very exciting news to the plaza quickly.</description></item><item><title>Page</title><link>https://markpaulayers.com/page/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://markpaulayers.com/page/</guid><description>Duis duis sunt incididunt cupidatat non est veniam qui non sunt sunt proident exercitation. Fugiat tempor cillum nulla nisi qui id tempor. Est proident occaecat velit amet nulla veniam aute ullamco. Et veniam minim eiusmod nostrud pariatur reprehenderit ad voluptate officia deserunt et magna mollit excepteur.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://markpaulayers.com/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://markpaulayers.com/about/</guid><description>Colophon Exercitation enim consectetur pariatur officia esse. Elit sit minim cillum mollit consectetur ad ut eu elit officia Lorem. In eu consequat adipisicing occaecat. Commodo velit aliquip qui exercitation nisi cillum veniam voluptate voluptate ut aute. Ullamco minim aliquip voluptate commodo deserunt ipsum mollit.
Contact FIRST LAST ADDRESS LINE ONE CITY, ST 12345 UNITED STATES OF AMERICA name@example.com +1.707.555.1212</description></item><item><title>Markdown syntax</title><link>https://markpaulayers.com/articles/markdown-syntax/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://markpaulayers.com/articles/markdown-syntax/</guid><description>This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.
Headings The following HTML &amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;—&amp;lt;h6&amp;gt; elements represent six levels of section headings. &amp;lt;h1&amp;gt; is the highest section level while &amp;lt;h6&amp;gt; is the lowest.
H1 H2 H3 H4 H5 H6 Paragraph Xerum, quo qui aut unt expliquam qui dolut labo.</description></item></channel></rss>